Thank you so much for the day that we can serve you and serve our community.
Follow me, we're celebrating our practice week, our independence, and follow me just
giving you the thanks of the glory to decide to thank you for our freedoms and the
freedom that we had to live in our community.
Follow us, we'll look after our service man and we'll bet that it protect us and we're done.
We just asked you to remember those, you're a fallen for us, and we gave you a lot.
Followed this by the start meeting, and by the start meeting.
Thank you, thank you.
Thank you.
I play the way you did to the flag that the United States of America and to the Republic for which it stands.
One nation, under God, in the visible, with every need and justice.
Thank you.
Neil.
Hello.
Let's get you a portion of the practice, and when the audience it wishes to address the authority on any of the agenda items.
You're being known out in five as a consent agenda staff, if you're recommending item six through nine for the consent agenda.
If there are no questions at the end of the motion to allow motion.
Would you go further?
Okay.
And a second.
Second.
Go call please.
Johnson.
Weston.
Aye.
Forster.
Lewis.
Aye.
Choks.
That takes us to item 10, which is a new business and a new business.
Do you know anyone?
No.
Item 11 is staff report, which was during the packet, and staff available for questions if there are any.
Item 12 is trustee community announcements and the announcements that we need to make.
Do you have a good rodeo, despite the rain?
I think.
I think so.
I think it was a little bit of a damn hope, and it was a little bit of a challenge, but it still came off, especially.
You consider the flooding and now revenue.
It was tough for.
Interesting.
Challenging weekend.
Yeah.
Item 12.
That's a trustee community announcement.
Item 13 is a gentleman.
Do we have a motion to adjourn?